Sir. Parents are gathering out there.
It's been 22 days!
My son, Hong Jinyang,
is still nowhere to be seen!
I only have one child.
What am I going to do
if something happens to him?
My son…
It has been…
Officer!
-Officer.
-Where is my child?
Please. Officer!
Don't do that.
Please.
-Find my child.
-Everyone.
Everyone. Please calm down.
We are as anxious as you.
We haven't slept for a few days.
Creating a ruckus here
is not going to solve the problem, is it?
-Go. Tear it down.
-Okay.
-No! Don't!
-Who dares to tear it down!
No!
Who said you could tear it down?
Keep the posters up.
Will tearing the posters down
solve the problem?
Will it locate the children?
Citizens can post whatever they want.
Use your expertise
if you want to bring the posters down.
My fellow parents.
I am Zhao Jie,
Captain of the Criminal Department
in Nanshan Branch.
Today, I will give you my word
that within seven days,
we will solve the case
and give you an answer.
If we fail to do so,
I will step down.
I'll take your word for it.
Thank you so much!
-No need to do this.
-Please.
Thank you.
MISSING PERSON
WEIYANG PUBLIC
SECURITY BUREAU NANSHAN BRANCH
FAIR AND JUST, LOYAL AND TRUE
MISSING PERSONS SPECIAL TASK FORCE
We have questioned everyone
from the illegal internet cafe
in Yuanlongli.
None of the 18 are under suspicion.
All five teenagers went missing
after they skipped classes.
Three of them
last appeared
at the illegal internet cafe.
The victims don't know each other.
They couldn't possibly have
planned together to go
missing voluntarily.
One of them was injured
and is currently traumatized.
We can basically conclude
that it's a serial kidnapping case.
Captain Zhao made a promise yesterday.
We only have seven days.
We must find
these kids within seven days,
even if we have
to turn the entire city upside down.
Good. Speak.
Captain Qu. If this is the doing
of a serial kidnapper,
can we release a statement to the school
clarifying that Han Zi'ang
is the victim of the kidnapping,
and he only attacked someone
out of fear and shock?
You there.
Handle this matter.
Yes, sir!
Let's circle back.
Captain Zhao wants us
to submit a new investigation plan.
Let's work together and brainstorm.
You can still take more pawns.
-Dad.
-That's right.
Hey.
So?
Got your assignment?
Nothing.
Other than a few side-eyes.
Qu Dahai doesn't have
what it takes to solve cases.
He learned a few tricks from Ran
and began to show off.
Sooner or later,
he'll lead the case to a dead end.
We're having an emergency.
Stop saying something unhelpful.
But Ran's theory is still useful.
Everything has a center.
And outside the center,
there will be ripples.
Dad. I've read the book thrice.
What are you getting at?
CHAPTER 2: "EYE OF THE VORTEX THEORY"
To see the eye of the vortex,
you must be part of it.
The Eye of the Vortex Theory.
Officer He,
I don't know anything
about investigations.
But allow me to thank you
on behalf of the school.
If you hadn't defended
Han Zi'ang this relentlessly,
this turn of events
wouldn't have occurred at all.
Right now, the students
and the parents no longer view Han Zi'ang
as a problematic student,
but as a hero who fought
against the kidnapper.
Principal Qin.
I still need your help
to identify the culprit.
Me?
DANFENG MIDDLE SCHOOL
Class, stand!
-Good morning, sir.
-Sit down.
Open your geometry textbooks.
Let's have a recap
of what we learned previously.
Bye, sir.
Bye.
Miss, are you role-playing as Han Zi'ang?
Yes.
He isn't as spirited as you are.
He spends half of his day sleeping.
Then what does he do
for the rest of his day?
Reading comics. His mind
lives in another dimension.
Xuan. Over here.
Han Zi'ang is a weirdo, right?
Yes. We can't understand
what he says at all.
I think he's obsessed with a cosplayer.
He even said he'd attend
a comic convention
in Shanghai during summer break.
No need to search online.
His interest has changed.
He is now a fan of an anime.
Right. He loves… What is she called again?
Nangong…
This one here.
Yes! Nangong Xuanyue.
NANGONG XUANYUE
TOGETHER FOR YOUR HEALTH
UNITED IN TRUST AND CARE
Drink some water.
Everyone at school
knows you're the victim.
Principal Qin said you were very brave.
They are looking forward to your return.
Ang.
Do you hear me?
Xuanyue.
You've come back.
He Xiaohe!
-Calm down.
-He Xiaohe!
-You can't go in.
-You can't enter.
-Let me.
You can't enter.
There's no one else inside.
We've brought everyone out.
Please calm down.
POLICE
Uncle Ran.
Are you injured?
Keyboard!
Keyboard…
Where were you?
Hey!
She was at my place.
Who are you?
Why was she at your place?
What did you do to her?
-She clung to me!
-Tell me!
-What did you do to her?
-Stop!
-Let go!
-Do you know how old she is?
Let go…
What is wrong with you?
-He's my friend, not a criminal!
-Come.
Come back with me.
-Come!
-No! Let go of me!
I won't come back with you.
You don't even know what happened.
Don't just assume everything.
So much for thinking
you are my best friend!
Xiaohe!
Double Stripe.
You peed here last time.
I've held a lot this time. Let's compete.
-You? Maybe after you beat Bunny first.
-Come.
Come.
Ready.
Three.
Two.
Why did you shout?
What is that?
What…
It… It might be a person.
It is a person.
I've never met her.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
-Hurry up.
-Hurry.
Open the shutter.
Open it.
Put her in here.
JIAJIA GROCERY
Mister, we found a frozen girl.
Bring her inside.
Don't freeze her to death.
-Come.
-Fine.
One, two, three.
Let's go.
Careful.
TUNZHOU CITY
TUNZHOU LOCAL FAVORITES
Mister.
-A bowl of noodles, please.
-Sure. Please go inside.
Enjoy. Careful. It's hot.
Mister,
do you know
any unique places in Tunzhou,
or maybe a place
photographers love to visit?
There are plenty of them.
Look.
We have Yongji Bridge,
Sanyi Temple, Zhang Fei's Shrine,
and this, Tunzhou Twin Towers.
-Mister. Can I have some pepper?
-Sure.
YONGJI BRIDGE
SANYI TEMPLE, ZHANG FEI'S SHRINE
Mister.
Any place that is quite desolate?
A place that has been abandoned for years.
What a peculiar preference.
Here.
This one here?
COPPER FACTORY
Copper Factory.
JIAJIA GROCERY
CONVENIENT AND AFFORDABLE
Send in the soldiers.
Bunny.
This girl is so fierce.
Wake up!
You…
Who are you? Who the heck are you?
-Who are you?
-Help!
Who are you?
Stop hitting him. Stop hitting him.
-Get her!
-Bring it on!
Bring it on!
Don't try to mess with me.
Stop!
Don't come any closer!
Hello?
Hello, Dad.
Xiaohe.
Where are you calling me from?
The shop by the school's gate.
It's so late now.
Why aren't you at school?
Why are you calling me?
Nothing.
Then I'll hang up now.
My phone is dying.
Go back to your class.
Finish your homework and eat on time.
Listen to Uncle Ran.
Do you hear me?
Hello?
She's skipping classes again.
Keyboard. You're gone.
The band is gone.
No one at home cares about me.
Where should I go now?
If you really want to learn music,
you can go to Beijing.
Go home now.
This place is not an orphanage.
Exactly.
Please don't kick me out.
My dad…
I was adopted.
My dad hits me every day
and forces me to drop out of school.
I'm too scared to go home.
I want to work
to pay for my tuition.
What a rough childhood.
No wonder she's so violent.
Mister, help her out.
She has to work to fund her studies.
That's already tough enough.
Mister, let me help you in your shop.
I only have one rule.
The internet cafe
downstairs is unlicensed.
So don't mess it up for me.
You must be Wan Qiming.
POLICE
So, you found me after all.
I met her through a magazine.
We were pen pals.
We wrote more than
ten letters to each other.
We had feelings for each other.
So, we decided to meet up.
It became official then.
I began to look for a job in Weiyang.
She's a bit color-blind.
So I only took monochrome photos of her.
As time went by, it became a habit.
I don't take colored photos anymore.
Around three months after we met,
she brought me home.
Her relatives were quite fond of me.
Her father was eccentric,
but he didn't say no to it.
Everything was going so well.
Qiming.
Let's get married.
Meng.
Come with me to Guangdong.
I'd love to marry you,
but I don't have a career now.
Weiyang is too small.
I don't want to stay here
doing wedding photography forever.
Let's work hard for a few years.
Once our careers are stable,
we'll get married.
What's the matter?
I don't want a career.
I just want a family.
But we're still young.
We can prove ourselves.
-Do you know that--
-Qiming.
I can't leave my dad.
Can you stay in Weiyang?
In the end, I decided
to head to Guangdong.
We separated
and resumed our written communication,
as we did before.
Then she said she'd wait for me,
that once I earned enough money,
I'd return to Weiyang to marry her.
I said yes.
And then?
After more than six months,
she stopped replying to my letters.
I called her home,
but no one would pick up.
During the Qingming Festival of 1996,
I told my mentor
that I wanted to return home
to pay respect to my ancestors.
But in fact, I went
to Weiyang to look for her.
That's when I learned
that she and her father
were in the accident at Mount Wu.
To treat her dad, she took out loans.
But what I couldn't accept
was that Xu Zhihong
forced his daughter to…
For his medical bill.
Meng.
Come with me.
Let's go to Guangdong.
Just leave.
I don't mind what you used to do.
My career is blooming right now.
We'll get married
once we arrive in Guangdong.
We'll build a family. Okay?
Please?
I gave you a chance back then.
Now, there's no way I can leave Weiyang.
Why do you want
to stay in this broken home of yours?
My dad is back. Go inside.
Go inside.
You jerk.
You dumped Meng and ran away.
I knew you were not a good man.
Why are you back?
What do you want?
To lure her away with your lies again?
Dad. He came back to visit me.
He'll leave soon.
-Move aside!
-He'll leave soon.
Bugger off!
Bugger off! Bugger off! Bugger off!
Do not touch me!
You're a father.
Yet you forced your daughter
to sell her body.
What kind of man are you?
Who are you to judge me?
This is my home. I have the final say.
As long as I still live,
you will not take Meng away.
Dad, sit down.
-Bugger off!
-Dad.
Just go! Dad.
I wasn't willing to let it go initially,
so I hired the neighbor
opposite them to spy on them
and see what's going on every day.
Actually, I was hoping
that the old man would die soon.
What did your informant tell you?
Nothing in particular.
Just that she kept working
in that line of work.
If one place was busted,
she would find another.
And then?
Then, a few months ago, I saw the news
that her father had died.
Xu Zhihong was a selfish man.
Did he not deserve death?
Did he not deserve to be killed?
Do you think Xu Meng is dead?
I'm not sure about that.
But when we were pen pals, I had a hunch
that she had other pen pals.
She is the kind of girl
who likes to be doted on.
She has a temper.
She is prideful.
Girls like her, in that line of work,
will offend a lot of people.
Mr. Officer, I've told you
everything I can.
I didn't kill Xu Zhihong.
And I'd never hurt Xu Meng.
Xu Meng and her father
went missing the day before
the Hong Kong handover.
My mentor took a gig back then
and brought me to Hong Kong to shoot
the lives of the Hong Kong citizens
before the reunification.
I was already away by the middle of June.
I have an alibi.
Zhao Jie.
I was looking for you.
This is the department's
annual budget. Please sign it.
I'm here to report a case.
He Xiaohe, resident of Unit 401,
Block 7, Ward 12, Poluo Street,
13 years old, might have gone missing.
I thought it was something serious.
-That's just Xiaohe being Xiaohe.
-Exactly.
She runs away every few days.
Okay. Report received.
-Chen. Register it right away.
-Okay.
Before she went missing, she was with me.
A good friend of hers
died in a fire in the bar.
She is probably traumatized.
I've heard about it.
The victim was locked in the storeroom.
Someone next door didn't
extinguish their cigarette properly,
and it fell on the carpet.
The fire burned everything.
The victim was called Keyboard.
I knew him too.
Check every location on this list.
Mobilize the officers
with Mangkun as soon as possible.
Okay.
Here. Take a look.
Chen, have you registered the case?
The important information is in it.
-Have you seen this girl?
-No.
Take a look. Have you seen this girl?
-Let me see.
-Take a look.
She's this tall. Around 13 years old.
DRUMS, PERCUSSION
Sir, this is
the security footage for today.
Can you fast forward it?
-Sure.
-Fast forward it.
Let me skim through it.
SUNDAY
WEIYANG PARK, WEIYANG SQUARE
NANSHAN SUPERMARKET, WEIYANG BOOK STORE…
WEIYANG TRAIN STATION
CALLS
MENTOR
The number you're dialing
has been switched off.
Please try again later.
END CALL
POLICE
-Check inside.
-Okay.
WEIYANG BUS TERMINAL
Don't mind me.
RIVERSIDE MARKET
How am I supposed to go back to Ran now?
It's so cold now.
Where could she have gone?
She has always been
a hyperactive troublemaker.
I'm sure she's fine.
JIAJIA GROCERY
CHINESE CHESS
See you.
Come back again.
Thank you.
Little girl, do you have cigarettes here?
No. Only snacks and drinks.
Can you get me two soft packs of Yuxi?
You can keep the change.
Yuxi is 21 yuan a pack.
This is a huge deal.
Thank you, mister.
I'll get your cigarettes now.
-Look after this for me.
-Okay.
ROUTE 36 TRAIN STATION TO MALL STREET
Keyboard.
How are you on the other side?
Make sure you're practicing there too.
You will be the best keyboardist ever.
Also,
don't be a chicken.
You'll get bullied like this.
POLICE
MOUNT WU TOURIST AREA
A three-day trip to Mount Wu.
Come take a look.
It's our new offer.
Have you heard of it?
Sir. Sir.
New offer, new promotion.
Come take a look.
-Do you go to the train station?
-Come in.
Sir!
Sir. It has been a few tough years.
Give me a chance. Take a look.
Thank you.
KUNPENG TRAVEL AGENCY
We have a new offer.
Sorry.
New offer, new promotion.
Coming!
When is the next departure date?
Which one?
The three-day Mount Wu trip.
KUNPENG TRAVEL AGENCY, MOUNT WU TOUR
FRIDAY DEPARTURES, 3-DAY TRIP
JIAJIA GROCERY
I bought you an egg each.
Come get your nutrition.
You've worked so hard.
Have you earned enough
for your tuition fee?
Truth be told,
I'm trying
to save for my train ticket to Beijing.
To Beijing?
Are you going there
to study at Tsinghua University?
Little girl.
The usual, please.
You can keep the change.
Thank you, mister.
Wait.
The beer is on me.
I'm a Buddhist. I don't drink.
Thank you, though.
SPICY CHICKEN BITES
WITH SECRET FAMILY RECIPE
Sorry.
He Xiaohe. Is that a cigarette pack I see?
Stay right there!
He Xiaohe. Stay right there.
YUXI CIGARETTE
She can run.
Stay right there.
Stop. Stay right there.
Stop.
He Xiaohe. Stop.
You really can run.
Let's see where you can go now.
I'll stay.
-Bye, sir.
-You…
1.4 meters. This tall.
Take a look.
Mister.
Zhao Jie.
Captain Ran. Qu.
It was very cold that night.
She couldn't have run far.
Focus on the 24-hour shops
within the red circles.
Let's split up and search.
It'll be more efficient.
Mangkun, Chen. You guys go here.
I'll take this one. Okay?
-Okay.
-Split the workload among yourselves.
Hi, Mr. Zhang.
Hello?
Are you the parent of He Xiaohe?
She didn't come to class today.
I saw her running around with cigarettes.
Will you please discipline her?
When? Where did you see her?
Tell me more.
I see.
Forgive me, Mr. Zhang.
I'll lecture her later.
Xiaohe has appeared.
Someone saw her
buying cigarettes at Nanhu Market.
They even found
bus tickets in her pockets.
Nanhu Market.
Bus tickets.
And cigarettes too?
Check all bus stations
that serve Nanhu Market.
Okay.
NANHU MARKET